fun.com 2019-10-16

# Privacy Policy

Thanks for visiting Fun.com, Inc.'s Privacy Policy. We are updating our Policy effective on 08/08/2019. Some of the changes you will see:

  * We've added a section about select partners.
  * We've updated the technologies we use.
  * We’ve removed outdated technologies and information that was no longer applicable.

We previously updated our Policy effective on 02/13/2019. Some of the changes you will see:

  * We've added a section about submitting product reviews

We previously updated our Policy effective on 05/25/2018. Some of the changes you will see:

  * We’ve removed outdated technologies and information that was no longer applicable.
  * We’ve reorganized and edited the Policy so that it’s easier to read and more transparent about what personal information we collect, how we collect it, and how we use it.
  * We’ve added information specifically for our European Union customers to align with GDPR requirements.

Though our Privacy Policy has changed, our commitment to your privacy and protecting your information has not, including our promise to never sell your data.

## Table Of Contents

  * Changes to This Policy
  * Who We Are
  * How This Policy Applies
  * Information We Collect
    * Information You Provide Directly to Us
    * Website Analytics
    * Cookies, Tracking, and Advertising
  * Product Reviews
    * Terms & Conditions for Photo Sharing
  * How We Use This Information
    * Providing Products/Services
    * How We Use Website Analytics Data
    * How We Use Cookies, Tracking Data, and Advertising
  * How This Information Is Shared
    * Information Shared Publicly
    * Fulfilling Your Order
    * Affiliate Tracking
    * Third-Party Hosting Provider
    * Links to Other Websites
    * Additional Disclosure
    * Select Partners
  * Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information
  * Security
  * Data Retention
  * Contact Information
  * California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights
  * Children’s Online Privacy
  * European Union Residents
    * Lawful Basis
    * Your Choices: Data Access, Correction, Deletion, and Portability
    * Your Rights: Restricting Processing and Objection

## Changes to This Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Who We Are

We are Fun.com, Inc., owned and operated in North Mankato, Minnesota, USA. We provide online shopping for a variety of specialty products on the following websites:

  * Additional themed costume sites

## How This Policy Applies

This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect on our websites when you place an order or sign up for our email list, the anonymous information that we collect as you browse our website, why we collect it, and our legal basis for doing so. It also covers the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. Because Fun.com, Inc. is a US-based company, your information will be collected, processed, and stored in the United States. The United States has its own laws governing data protection and government access to information. The rules that protect your personal information under United States law may be different than in your home country. When using any of our services you consent to the collection, transfer, disclosure, storage, and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed, or if you have any questions or feedback, please contact Fun.com, Inc. here.

## Information We Collect

### Information You Provide Directly to Us

We collect the following personal information from you when you place an order:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, shipping address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as billing address and credit card information
  * The company name of your business, when shipping to a business address

We collect the following personal information from you when you sign up for an account:

  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Contact Information such as name, shipping address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as billing address

We collect the following personal information from you when you sign up for our product notifications or marketing emails:

  * Email address

We collect the following personal information from you when you contact our customer service department via the contact us form or live chat:

  * Name, email address, and order number

You may decline to provide us with your information in any of these cases. However, this will limit your ability to register for an account, receive emails, or to place an order.

### Website Analytics

As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, and your interaction with different pages of our website. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

### Cookies, Tracking, and Advertising

Like many websites, we use cookies and similar technologies in order to provide our shopping experience and also to track and improve our services. Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are utilized by Fun.com, Inc. and the third-party analytics platforms that we use to optimize your shopping experience. These platforms include:

  * Bronto (our email provider)
  * Rich Relevance (product recommendations we show on our website)
  * Google Analytics (tracks how customers use our website)

Additionally, we partner with third-parties to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on our website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. These platforms include:

  * Adroll
  * Bing Remarketing
  * Facebook Remarketing
  * Google Adwords Remarketing
  * Google Dynamic Remarketing

Finally, our website includes Social Media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly.

## Product Reviews

Fun.com, Inc. values your feedback and invites you to rate and review any purchases made on our websites. If you choose to write a review, please be sure to explain why you like or dislike the product, focusing on the product’s features and your experience with the product. If you upload a photo or video along with your review, please read through the Photo Sharing terms and conditions below, as they do apply to all submissions. If you’re looking to comment about product selection, pricing, ordering, delivery or any other issues related to ordering or website maintenance, please contact our customer service.

CUSTOMER SERVICE HOURS:  
24 Hours a Day!

## Terms & Conditions for Photo Sharing

By submitting a photograph or video (we’ll refer to both of them as “photograph” from now on) to Fun.com, Inc., you thereby agree to our use of submitted photograph(s) according to these Terms of Use, and you also agree that you have read and fully understand these Terms of Use and will comply with them in their entirety. Those terms are as follows:

  1. Please do not send or upload photographs that you didn’t take yourself or don’t have permission to send or upload. By submitting you agree that you have taken the photograph yourself and own the copyright in the photograph, or have received the express permission of the copyright owner to have the photograph used and shared by Fun.com, Inc. in accordance with these Terms of Use.
  2. You agree that you have express permission of everyone who appears in the photograph to be photographed and have the photograph used and shared by Fun.com, Inc. in accordance with these Terms of Use. 
  3. You keep all of your ownership rights to any photograph or other content but give Fun.com, Inc. permission to use the photograph as determined by Fun.com, Inc. By submitting, or otherwise agreeing to our use of, a photograph or other content, including but not limited to photo captions and your name, (collectively, “Content”), you grant Fun.com, Inc. the worldwide, unrestricted, royalty-free, irrevocable, sub-licensable right to (a) publish, publicly display and perform, modify, edit, alter and otherwise use the Content in whole or in part, without further consent, review or participation from you, for any purpose throughout the world (including commercial and promotional) in any medium or format now existing or hereafter created, including but not limited to print or recorded material, websites, and social media platforms; and (b) use your name, commentary, and other information about you in connection with the Content. Fun.com, Inc. reserves the right to use, not use, or discontinue using any Content in our sole discretion at any time.
  4. You agree not to submit any Content that: a. Infringes any intellectual property rights of any other person or third party, including but not limited to copyright and trademark. b. Defames or invades the privacy or publicity rights of any person, living or deceased, or infringes upon any person’s or third party’s personal, property, or other right. c. Is inappropriate, sexually explicit, harassing, abusive, harmful, violent, or otherwise objectionable or offensive in any way. d. Contains any virus, worm, corrupt file, or other forms of malicious code or content that may harm a website or computer. e. Violates any law, statute, ordinance, or regulation. f. Contains advertising, spam, references to other websites or retailers. g. Contains personal information such as e-mail addresses, phone numbers or physical addresses.
  5. Upon submission you irrevocably waive all rights and agree to release and hold harmless Fun.com, Inc. from any and all claims, costs, expenses, damages, causes of action and/or liabilities, of any nature, whether direct or indirect, known or unknown, foreseen or unforeseen, arising out of or relating to the Content, including but not limited to defamation; invasion of the rights of privacy or publicity; violation or any moral or artist rights; personal injury, or any other similar matter. You further agree to indemnify, defend, and hold Fun.com, Inc. harmless from any claim or cause of action related to your violation of any these Terms of Use.

If you have a disagreement with Fun.com, Inc. or believe that any of your Content has been used without your permission or in violation of your rights, you can reach Fun.com, Inc. at:

PHONE:  
507-386-8383

ADDRESS:  
2080 Lookout Drive  
North Mankato, MN 56003

FAX:  
507-386-0517

EMAIL:  
Contact Form

## How We Use This Information

### Providing Products/Services

We only use the information you provide to us for the specific purpose which you provided it to us – for example, we will not send you marketing emails because you initiated a live chat with customer service. We will use your information to:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation email
  * Send you a shipping notification email
  * Administer your account or process returns and refunds
  * Send you product or service information emails, if requested
  * Send you marketing communications, if requested
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our website and marketing efforts
  * Display content based upon your interests

### How We Use Website Analytics Data

We have implemented Google Analytics, Google Display Advertising, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting on our website to help us understand how visitors use our services. These tools use cookies to gather standard Internet log information and user behavior information in an anonymous form. The information created by the cookie about your use of the website is transmitted to Google and is then used to evaluate visitors' use of the website and to compile aggregate statistical reports on website activity for our site specifically. We have followed Google's best practice for IP Anonymization to ensure that no personally-identifiable information will be sent to Google Analytics. See [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en) for more detail.

We will never (nor will we allow any third-party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personal Information of visitors to our website. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google, nor will Google link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personal Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.

If you would like to opt out of being tracked using Google Analytics on any website, then simply head over to [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and install the add-on in your browsers.

### How We Use Cookies, Tracking Data, and Advertising

We use cookies to keep track of user shopping carts, to remember our user's preferences (e.g. language and country preference), and for security/login authentication. These cookies are required in order for our website to function correctly and for you to place an order.

The third-party analytics platforms that we use on our website may set cookies on your computer. We utilize these technologies to analyze shopping and buying trends, to track users' interactions with the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole in order to provide an optimized shopping experience and relevant product recommendations. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. These cookies are optional; our website will function and you can place an order, though the content you see on the website may not be as relevant.

Our third-party advertising partners may use technologies such as cookies or beacons to gather information about your activities on our website. This information is used when you leave our website and visit a site that uses the same advertising partner. That website will then display product advertising to you based upon your browsing activities and interests while you were on our website. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

The Social Media features and widgets on our website are hosted by a third-party and may use cookies or beacons. These third-party cookies are set by the individual Social Media service and are used to provide the functionality of the feature as well as collect any additional tracking data. Please note that we do not send your personal information to these Social Media widgets, but they still have access to your web browsing information such as browser, operating system, and IP address. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Your browser may give you the ability to control the cookies that are set on your computer. If you block or delete cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. To find out more about how to enable, disable, or delete cookies from your web browser, please visit [here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

## How This Information Is Shared

We will share your personal information with third-parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We will never sell your personal information to third-parties.

### Information Shared Publicly

Our website offers a publicly accessible blog or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access it. The blog is moderated and you may have comments made by yourself removed by contacting us.

Any time you write a product review, the details of the review and the manner of which you identified yourself will be publicly accessible to anyone who views our product pages. Any information you provide may be read, collected, used, or responded to by others who access it. Product reviews are moderated and you may have reviews or comments made by yourself removed by contacting us.

All other information you provide to us will not be shared publicly.

### Fulfilling Your Order

We may provide your personal information to trusted third-party companies that provide services to fulfill your order, such as fraud detection and investigation, credit card processing, and order shipping. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us. These services include:

  * ThreatMetrix (fraud protection)
  * PayPal (credit card processing)
  * Amazon Pay (credit card processing)
  * Braintree (credit card processing)
  * Sezzle (“pay later” payment method)
  * FedEx (address validation and shipping service)
  * UPS (address validation and shipping service)
  * USPS (shipping service)

### Affiliate Tracking

When you come to our website via a link on one of our affiliates' websites, we are obliged to notify them of the transaction so that they can be paid a commission – this is known as conversion tracking. Your personal information is not transferred to these affiliates. Some of our affiliates include:

  * AvantLink
  * Commission Junction
  * LinkShare
  * Share-A-Sale

### Third-Party Hosting Provider

Our ordering system and shopping cart database is hosted on server hardware supplied by our IT solutions provider. When we collect your shipping and billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order, it is saved on this hardware. Our solution provider does not have access to view your data but does perform administrative functions on the server hardware used to collect it.

### Links to Other Websites

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of the websites owned by Fun.com, Inc. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

### Additional Disclosure

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process, or respond to a government request,
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or in the case of possible criminal acts or security threats,
  * if Fun.com, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third-party with your prior consent to do so

### Select Partners

If Fun.com, Inc. establishes any business partnerships with other trustworthy persons or entities, known as Select Partners, whom all have confirmed privacy policies consistent with our own. We may rent, exchange, share and/or cross reference information, including your contact information, enabling these Select Partners to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive direct marketing from us or from our Select Partners, or if you would like to opt out of our rental or exchange of your information with other marketers, please let us know by contacting us or calling (507) 386-8383

## Correcting And Updating Your Personal Information

To review, delete or update your personal information to ensure it is accurate or if you no longer desire our service, please sign in to the My Account area of the website and use the self-service tools, or you may contact us.

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, you can sign in to the My Account area of the website and use the self-service tools, or you may contact us. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

## Security

We take security seriously, and the security of your personal data is important to us. When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow industry-standard practices to protect the data, both during transmission and once we receive it – including full-site SSL. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us.

We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third-party payment option (PayPal; Amazon Pay; Sezzle). If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information (such as credit card information) collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third-party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy policy and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy policy before providing your information.

In the event of a data breach, we have a protocol in place for handling the breach and notifying customers and the supervisory authority. We do not store any credit card information when your card is authorized during checkout, so there isn't a chance of your card information being stolen in a data breach after your order is placed.

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce agreements.

We also collect and maintain aggregated, anonymized information which we may retain indefinitely to protect the safety and security of our website, improve our services, or comply with legal obligations.

## Contact Information

You can contact us by phone, mail or email:

HalloweenCostumes.com  
2080 Lookout Drive  
North Mankato, MN 56003  

PHONE:  
(507) 386-8383  
(24 Hours a Day!)

Contact Form

## California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

Under California law, our customers that are California residents may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third-parties for their direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, we do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third-parties for direct marketing purposes without their approval.

If at any time you wish to opt out of having your personal information shared with third-parties and/or receiving information from Fun.com, Inc. (via e-mail or postal mail) about new products, services, or promotions, you can do so. You can contact us through our contact form. Please indicate what publications or services you no longer wish to receive so that we may better address your needs.

## Children’s Online Privacy

Our website is not marketed to, nor do we knowingly collect or store personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected or received personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately.

## European Union Residents

At Fun.com, Inc. we take your privacy seriously and have taken steps to comply with the requirements defined in the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) that goes into effect on May 25th, 2018. Many of the requirements are outlined in different areas of this Privacy Policy, but this section highlights items that are unique or specific to our European audience.

### Lawful Basis

Data protection law in Europe requires a lawful basis for collecting and retaining personal information from citizens or residents of the European Economic Area. Our lawful bases include:

  * Contract: in order to fulfil the contract we have with you to provide the product/service that you requested, we need to use your personal data to charge your payment and to ship goods to you.
  * Legal obligation: we may need your data to comply with customs requests or to maintain tax audit records.
  * Legitimate interests: we have a good and fair reason to use your data in ways that are reasonably expected as part of running our business and that do not materially impact your rights, freedom, or interests. For example, we use identity, device, and location information to prevent fraud and to keep our services secure. And we analyze how users interact with our website so that we can better understand which features and design elements are working well and which are not working.

### Your Choices: Data Access, Correction, Deletion, and Portability

We provide you with reasonable access to the personal data that you may have provided through your use of our services. If you wish to access, modify, delete, or obtain a copy of your information, you may do so at any time by logging in to the My Account section of our website to make changes, or by clicking on the Manage Preferences link in any email we've sent you to modify your preferences. Alternatively, you may contact us via email or live chat, or by phone or mail using the options listed in the Contact Information section of this privacy policy, and we will be happy to help you.

Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in the active user database instantly, we may retail some information for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, for audit and compliance records, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so.

### Your Rights: Restricting Processing and Objection

At any time prior to us shipping out your order, you may withdraw your consent to process your data by contacting us and we will cancel your order. Once an order has shipped we are unable to cancel the processing of your data, but you have the same right to access, correct, delete, or obtain a copy of your data at any time using our self-service tools or by contacting us. Additionally, you have the ability to opt-out from all performance, social media, and advertising cookies on our website by using the Cookie Settings link on the bottom of all pages of our website.

At any time, you may object to the processing of your personal data, on legitimate grounds, except if otherwise permitted by applicable law. In most cases you are able to control these settings through our self-service tools, but as always you may contact us via email or live chat, or by phone or mail using the options listed in the Contact Information section of this privacy policy, and we will be happy to help you.
